CHRISTINE ONG

QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

CONTACT

+63 928 253 9101

 \vee

tinongfb@gmail.com

2

Quezon City, PH

LINKS

LINKEDIN

GITHUB

MY PERSONAL PAGE

SKILLS

Manual Testing

Blackbox/Functionality Testing

Mobile App Testing

JIRA

API Testing

Problem-Solving

Computer Literacy

LICENSE

PROFESSIONAL FOOD TECHNOLOGIST: License number 0000631

EDUCATION

BS FOOD TECHNOLOGY

University of the Philippines, Diliman

2009 - 2014

SUMMARY

I am a QA Engineer with 2 years of experience in test case creation and thorough execution of black-box and functionality tests. I have knowledge in basic Java and Structured Query Language (SQL). I am passionate about software testing and I plan to further expand my skills by exploring automated testing technologies such as Selenium, and JUnit.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

QA ENGINEER

Softwares Ventures, Inc.

Oct 2021 - Present

- Creating and refining Test Cases of various tools and web applications
- Functional and GUI testing of web applications in various browsers in Windows and their adaptability in mobile browsers (Android OS)
- Testing of batch programs in centOS (includes database management through SQL)
- Testing of mobile applications integrated with a web application and database (Cassandra)
- · API testing using Postman
- Verification of resolved issues (bug recording)
- Part of Agile setup daily scrum, JIRA kanban board management and poker planning
- Deployment of applications in Payara; deployment of docker images through terminal
- Projects tested under CI/CD: Timekeeper App (has mobile app and web app), KYC (integrated with Megamatcher)
- Underwent basic Java training and basic SQL and database management training

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST (FOOD INGREDIENTS)

Promax International Corporation

2016 - 2021

 Created various food sample prototypes (for the purpose of showcasing the company's functional food ingredients); food product innovation through sensory evaluation and discussion